### education

## about

# Sarah Cosentino

2015 - 2020

High school leaving qualification in scientific studies, IIS Nostro-Repaci, Villa San Giovanni (RC)

2020 - 2023

Bachelor's Degree in Communication Design, Politecnico di Milano

Hi! I'm Sarah, a 20-year-old visual designer studying Communication Design at Politecnico di Milano. While my focus has primarily been on digital artifacts, I also have a strong interest in print design.

My design approach centers around user experience and being user-centered. This has sparked my fascination with service design, especially gamification. I'm captivated by the idea of making interactions with products and services enjoyable for both designers and users.

#### Communication designer

19/07/2002 Born in Reggio Calabria, Italy Based in Milan

+39 392 325 0908 sarah.cosentino02@gmail.com Linkedin: sarah.cosentino

## experience

ott 2021 - apr 2022

Social Media Manager for Dynamis PRC, the racing team of Politecnico di Milano that competes in the international Formula Student championship

feb 2023 - mar 2023

Website development for Anthropogenic Narratives, an event/ exhibition held at Triennale Milano presenting the projects carried out in the C1 Final Synthesis Workshop of the Degree Course in Communication Design, School of Design, Politecnico di Milano (a.y. 2022-2023).

apr 2023

Cultural mediator for the exhibition "Surprise Party: carte blanche à Constance Guisset Studio!", at Institut français Milan, during the Milan Design Week 2023.

### skills

languages: italian (native) english (fluent)

adobe creative suite (photoshop, illustrator, indesign, lightroom, premiere, aftereffects) blender figma

programming languages: javascript, p5js, threejs c++